General Ning,
it's not like that.
-I was trying to--
-You
still dare to assassinate our general!
I... It's not like that.
I...
Can you stop stabbing me here?
I finally took care of the assassin,
only for Ning Yuanci
to mistake me for the killer.
Actor Xia Yimo,
your story mission as Madam Qin
has failed.
You only have two chances left.
I know how to count.
Then are you ready
to enter the next role?
Wait, let me catch my breath.
The first time...
I played the maid Xiaolan.
I must have accidentally
bumped into the killer
assassinating Xue Ruowan,
which led to my tragic end.
The second time,
I played Cui Hu and was stabbed.
But Ning Yuanci didn't seem to know
the assassin would appear,
and even told me to kill the assassin.
I am not.
The third time,
I transmigrated into Lady Qin.
But she and Ning Yuanci
simply didn't have the time
to make a move on Xue Ruowan.
But Xue Ruowan
unexpectedly fell into the lake and died.
Then,
the most suspicious person is...
How could I forget
such a key figure?
There is only one truth.
I think I know
what the answer is.
I've never won a lottery
in my entire life.
Whatever,
I'll just take a wild guess.
I actually drew
the hidden character, Xue Keying.
What did you...
what did you just make me drink?
You actually drugged me.
Drugged?
Could I
be...
Muscle-relaxing powder again.
Help!
Do family drama series have to include
drugging plots?
What... what are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
It's... it's none of my business.
If you want to blame someone,
blame those who force
intimate scenes into the script.
Oh right,
I have the antidote.
Quick,
take this.
Come on.
Are you alright?
Xue Keying,
you really didn't have to do this.
Even though
I am to marry Xue Ruowan tomorrow,
I have no feelings
for her at all.
All you do is brainwash women.
So you bear no responsibility
at all?
Wait.
Tonight is the night before the wedding.
Sun Xiaofei!
Let go!
I won't!
Help!
Somebody help!
Someone is dead!
My Lady...
My Lady fell into the lake and died!
Wait.
I see.
Someone is trying to frame you.
Xue Keying, what are you doing?
Forgive me.
Ning Yuanci!
It's alright now.
The danger has passed.
Xue Ruowan!
You can come out now.
I forgot I tied you up there.
Xue Keying,
what on earth are you trying to do?
I...
I will explain it to you later.
Did you arrange
the assassins?
No.
Those assassins clearly
wanted to kill her.
How could she have arranged it?
Xue Keying said
someone used my sword
to frame
me.
So,
you poisoned me and Xue Keying.
You did all this
just to avoid marrying me.
Poisoning? Assassins?
I know absolutely nothing about this!
You are overthinking.
Xue Ruowan is just
a frail cripple.
How could she be capable of this?
Based on my deduction,
the assassin should be...
I can't let him suspect
Xue Ruowan,
or she'll end up badly
just like me.
I haven't read the script either.
God knows who the assassin is.
How am I supposed to make this up?
It's a spy from the Northern Border.
My father said
the General has been clearing out spies
from the Northern Border lately.
I have made many enemies.
That person obviously wanted to kill you.
Probably because they couldn't beat you,
they
targeted your bride instead.
General,
you must investigate this thoroughly.
Before we find out the truth,
I think we should
cancel tomorrow's wedding.
Just in case something else goes wrong.
The wedding can be delayed,
but it's impossible
for the Xue family to back out.
Rest assured, General.
I won't burden my father,
nor will I implicate the Xue family.
Since I have agreed,
I will never go back on my word.
Is this wedding plot
really necessary?
I never expected such a thing
to happen on the wedding day.
Fortunately, Wan'er is safe and sound.
However,
General, bringing your men
to search my residence
is perhaps inappropriate.
The assassin is not in my manor.
I fear that if this happens again,
both you, Duke, and I will lose face.
And we won't be able
to explain it to His Majesty.
The search is merely routine.
In case the assassin
left any clues behind.
Rest assured, Duke.
If it truly is Northern spies
seeking revenge on me,
I will uproot them
without mercy.
You jinx.
You brought thieves here
before you even got married.
Even if you marry the general,
you'll just be a curse to him.
If Ning Yuanci hadn't
forced me to marry him,
why would I suffer
such an unprovoked disaster?
How dare you talk back to Madam?
Exactly.
I'll tear your mouth apart.
Stop!
How come whenever I look away,
you're getting beaten up again?
At least fight back a little.
Don't pretend to be the good guy here.
Who knows what you and your mother
are plotting again?
How dare you bully my Ying'er?
I...
Your Highness,
stop.
Listen to me, all of you.
I don't like Ning Yuanci anymore.
From now on,
no one is allowed to bully or beat
Xue Ruowan in this residence.
Ying'er,
are you alright?
Mother.
I'm fine.
And also,
stop saying
she brings bad luck to her husband.
I think Ning Yuanci is the one
who brings bad luck to his wives.
Whoever marries him is doomed.
At this rate,
I've lost three lives
before the first episode is even over.
How am I supposed to survive
until the finale?
How could I forget the male lead?
According to the plot of Mo Xiang,
the female lead Xue Ruowan
breaks free from the shackles
of feudal marriage,
and runs a painting
and calligraphy business
with her childhood sweetheart,
Chu Qingyun.
After going through hardships,
they finally get together.
Does that mean as long as I find
the male lead,
I can push the plot forward
quickly?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't looking where I was going.
Where did these flowers come from?
Have I seen you
somewhere before?
I am Chu Qingyun,
a traditional Chinese painter.
I'm here to deliver a painting
to the Duke.
You are Chu Qingyun?
Handsome,
do you have time to do me a favor?
Am I not attractive enough?